(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
(شاهد على www.kisskh.li دعم الإدارة)
SOLD OUT ON YOU
نفدت الكمية لديك
Fine.
بخير.
I'm in Deokpung, so I should follow their stupid rules.
أنا في دوكبونغ، ​​لذا يجب عليّ اتباع قواعدهم السخيفة.
I'll reverse my car then.
سأقوم بإرجاع سيارتي للخلف إذن.
What was that? What happened?
ما هذا؟ ماذا حدث؟
Hey, what's going on?
مرحباً، ما الذي يحدث؟
Stop pressing that! Can't you see I'm trying to move?
توقف عن الضغط على ذلك! ألا ترى أنني أحاول التحرك؟
What's with him?
ما به؟
I can't believe this.
لا أصدق هذا.
Aren't you moving your car?
ألا تقوم بتحريك سيارتك؟
I'm sure you can squeeze through.
أنا متأكد من أنك تستطيع المرور.
You can't just leave like this.
لا يمكنك المغادرة هكذا.
I'm in a hurry right now,
أنا في عجلة من أمري الآن،
so hit or push through my car if you want.
لذا اضرب سيارتي أو ادفعها من خلالها إن شئت.
Oh, right.
أوه، صحيح.
My car's pretty expensive.
سيارتي غالية الثمن.
You should keep that in mind.
يجب أن تضع ذلك في اعتبارك.
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
Excuse me!
اعذرني!
Where's the mushroom farm?
أين تقع مزرعة الفطر؟
Where in the world is it?
أين يقع هذا المكان في العالم؟
Walking like this is a bit better.
المشي بهذه الطريقة أفضل قليلاً.
Damn it. Why did they want me to sell these?
اللعنة! لماذا أرادوا مني بيع هذه الأشياء؟
Geez, my feet are aching.
يا إلهي، قدماي تؤلمانني.
Why are you following me?
لماذا تلاحقني؟
-What? -Why are you following me?
- ماذا؟ - لماذا تتبعني؟
I'm just headed this way.
أنا متجه إلى هنا.
I think he really is following me.
أعتقد أنه يلاحقني بالفعل.
Damn it.
عليك اللعنة.
You really are following me.
أنت حقاً تتابعني.
I'm just passing by.
أنا أمر من هنا فقط.
I can't believe it.
لا أصدق ذلك.
I've had men follow me in their sports cars before,
سبق أن تبعني رجال بسياراتهم الرياضية،
but a tractor is a first.
لكن الجرار هو الأول من نوعه.
I'll admit it's pretty unique.
أعترف أنه فريد من نوعه إلى حد كبير.
But, sir,
لكن يا سيدي،
I'm really here to just meet someone important.
أنا هنا فقط لمقابلة شخص مهم.
So, please don't bother me anymore. I'm asking you very nicely.
لذا، أرجوك لا تزعجني بعد الآن. أطلب منك ذلك بكل لطف.
-Excuse me. -Geez, please stop.
-معذرةً. -يا إلهي، من فضلك توقف.
Wait, this is good. Let me ask you.
انتظر، هذا جيد. دعني أسألك.
-Do you know where the mushroom farm is? -Excuse me.
- هل تعرف أين تقع مزرعة الفطر؟ - معذرةً.
They're white flower noori mushrooms.
إنها فطر النوري ذو الزهرة البيضاء.
Over there? Where?
هناك؟ أين؟
Move over there so I can pass by!
ابتعد إلى هناك حتى أتمكن من المرور!
What… Oh, my gosh!
ماذا... يا إلهي!
What the…
يا إلهي...
Is he out of his mind?
هل فقد عقله؟
Excuse me! Hey!
معذرةً! مهلاً!
The mushrooms!
الفطر!
The white flower noori mushrooms!
فطر النوري ذو الزهرة البيضاء!
Excuse me! Sir!
معذرةً سيدي!
Just a moment, sir!
لحظة من فضلك يا سيدي!
Sir, let me just look…
سيدي، دعني ألقي نظرة...
So it can reverse!
إذن يمكن عكس العملية!
Damn it.
عليك اللعنة.
Hey, you said earlier your tractor couldn't reverse.
مهلاً، لقد قلتَ سابقاً أن جرارك لا يستطيع الرجوع للخلف.
-What do you want? -Well…
- ماذا تريد؟ - حسناً...
This seems like the mushroom farm. Is the owner inside--
يبدو هذا المكان كمزرعة فطر. هل المالك بالداخل؟
No.
لا.
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
You didn't even check if the owner is inside.
لم تتحقق حتى مما إذا كان المالك بالداخل.
If he was, this wouldn't be happening.
لو كان كذلك، لما حدث هذا.
What?
ماذا؟
When will the owner come then?
متى سيأتي المالك إذن؟
-He won't be here for a while. -What?
- لن يكون هنا لفترة من الوقت. - ماذا؟
-Hey. -In that case,
-مهلاً. -في هذه الحالة،
could you please contact him for me?
هل يمكنك الاتصال به نيابة عني؟
Fine. I'll tell him
حسناً. سأخبره
that someone extremely rude just barged in here.
لقد اقتحم شخص وقح للغاية هذا المكان للتو.
Well, it was my first time here, so…
حسناً، كانت هذه زيارتي الأولى هنا، لذا...
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
he hates people like that.
إنه يكره أمثال هؤلاء الناس.
I haven't introduced myself.
لم أقدم نفسي.
I'm a home shopping host from HIT Homeshopping.
أنا مقدمة برامج التسوق المنزلي من شركة HIT Homeshopping.
My name's Dam Ye-jin.
اسمي دام يي جين.
HIT HOMESHOPPING HOME SHOPPING HOST DAM YE-JIN
هيت هوم شوبينج، مقدمة برنامج التسوق المنزلي دام يي جين
What? What is he doing?
ماذا؟ ماذا يفعل؟
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
Where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
What is that?
ما هذا؟
What?
ماذا؟
Sir…
سيد…
I can't believe this guy.
لا أصدق هذا الرجل.
Geez!
يا إلهي!
Time will solve everything
سيحل الزمن كل شيء.
It's a bit dry today, so spray a lot of water.
الجو جاف قليلاً اليوم، لذا رشّ الكثير من الماء.
-All right. -There we go.
- حسناً. - ها نحن ذا.
A bit more gently.
بلطف أكثر قليلاً.
Okay.
تمام.
Mr. Park.
السيد بارك.
Hey, Mechoori.
مرحباً، ميتشوري.
You came back so quickly.
لقد عدت بسرعة كبيرة.
You didn't load a box of mushrooms.
لم تقم بتحميل صندوق من الفطر.
Gosh, I must have forgotten it.
يا إلهي، لا بد أنني نسيت ذلك.
Didn't I tell you to just focus on work?
ألم أقل لك أن تركز فقط على العمل؟
As the supervisor, you're supposed to oversee those things.
بصفتك مشرفًا، من المفترض أن تشرف على هذه الأمور.
I just played a bit of music to keep our energy up.
لقد شغّلت بعض الموسيقى فقط للحفاظ على حماسنا.
Kwang-mo got caught red-handed.
تم القبض على كوانغ مو متلبساً بالجرم المشهود.
I knew he would.
كنت أعرف أنه سيفعل ذلك.
It boosts metabolism and is an effective pest control--
يعزز عملية التمثيل الغذائي ويُعد وسيلة فعالة لمكافحة الآفات.
Mr. Park.
السيد بارك.
This will be used to make medicine and makeup products.
سيتم استخدام هذا في صناعة الأدوية ومستحضرات التجميل.
Slacking off like that is detrimental here.
إن التراخي بهذا الشكل ضار هنا.
I'll be careful from now on.
سأكون حذراً من الآن فصاعداً.
Power on.
تشغيل الطاقة.
I'm sorry
أنا آسف
This is the last time I'm letting this slide.
هذه هي المرة الأخيرة التي سأتغاضى فيها عن هذا الأمر.
Sorry.
آسف.
I'm sorry…
أنا آسف…
Mr. Park!
السيد بارك!
Oh, my gosh! These are the white flower noori mushrooms, right?
يا إلهي! هذه هي فطر النوري ذو الزهرة البيضاء، أليس كذلك؟
-You're still here? -I was about to go.
- ما زلت هنا؟ - كنت على وشك الذهاب.
But do you have any leftover slippers here?
لكن هل لديك أي نعال متبقية هنا؟
I'll pay full price for them.
سأدفع ثمنها كاملاً.
No.
لا.
Don't be like that. Just help me out.
لا تكن هكذا. فقط ساعدني.
I can't take another step in these heels.
لا أستطيع أن أخطو خطوة أخرى بهذه الأحذية ذات الكعب العالي.
You can't possibly make me keep walking in this condition, can you?
لا يمكنك إجباري على الاستمرار في المشي في هذه الحالة، أليس كذلك؟
Please.
لو سمحت.
Then, at least give me some plastic bags…
إذن، على الأقل أعطني بعض الأكياس البلاستيكية...
Why did you run in those heels anyway?
لماذا ركضتِ بتلك الأحذية ذات الكعب العالي على أي حال؟
I couldn't let my chance to meet the farm owner slip away.
لم أستطع أن أدع فرصة لقاء صاحب المزرعة تضيع مني.
Even if I broke my toes, I had to run.
حتى لو كسرت أصابع قدمي، كان عليّ أن أركض.
Follow me.
اتبعني.
No need to pay. Just take a pair of these.
لا داعي للدفع. خذ زوجًا من هذه فقط.
If you keep loitering,
إذا استمريت في التسكع،
I'll report you for obstructing business.
سأبلغ عنك بتهمة عرقلة سير العمل.
There's more in here.
يوجد المزيد هنا.
But…
لكن…
There's nothing I can wear…
لا يوجد شيء يمكنني ارتداؤه...
Geez…
يا إلهي...
Damn it.
عليك اللعنة.
How do they expect me to wear these?
كيف يتوقعون مني أن أرتدي هذه الملابس؟
I'm Dam Ye-jin.
أنا دام يي جين.
I don't back out once I've made up my mind.
لا أتراجع بمجرد أن أتخذ قراري.
What?
ماذا؟
What are they doing?
ماذا يفعلون؟
Are they stealing stuff?
هل يسرقون الأشياء؟
All right, then.
حسناً، إذاً.
Try anything funny,
جرب أي شيء مضحك،
and I'll tell on you to the owner.
وسأبلغ عنك للمالك.
Pop, pop
فرقعة، فرقعة
Twirling
الدوران
All done.
تم الانتهاء.
Mr. Park. Wait.
السيد بارك، انتظر.
What?
ماذا؟
There's still a lot left in here.
لا يزال هناك الكثير هنا.
You have to remove them cleanly.
يجب إزالتها بشكل نظيف.
It's okay to miss one or two.
لا بأس أن تفوتك واحدة أو اثنتان.
Mr. Park.
السيد بارك.
Those one or two you miss will cause mold
ستتسبب تلك النقطة أو النقطتان اللتان تغفل عنهما في حدوث العفن.
and ruin a whole substrate.
ويدمر طبقة الركيزة بأكملها.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
I have to head back,
عليّ العودة،
so make sure to clean these out properly.
لذا تأكد من تنظيفها بشكل صحيح.
But there's so much…
لكن هناك الكثير...
What?
ماذا؟
Rose.
وَردَة.
My dear Rose. I missed you so much!
عزيزتي روز، اشتقت إليكِ كثيراً!
Let's head back to Seoul--
لنعد إلى سيول --
What happened to your ear?
ماذا حدث لأذنك؟
Who did this to you?
من فعل هذا بك؟
No way!
مستحيل!
You can't just leave like this.
لا يمكنك المغادرة هكذا.
Hit or push through my car if you want.
اضرب سيارتي أو ادفعها من خلالها إن شئت.
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
That tractor!
ذلك الجرار!
He actually hit my car?
هل صدم سيارتي فعلاً؟
This is totally…
هذا أمرٌ...
That lunatic!
ذلك المجنون!
Hurry up and move your car.
أسرع وحرك سيارتك.
Do you know how busy farmers are? Don't block the darn road.
هل تعلم كم ينشغل المزارعون؟ لا تسد الطريق اللعين.
And it's so hot today. Come on.
الجو حار جداً اليوم. هيا.
Hurry up and move!
أسرعوا وتحركوا!
Right.
يمين.
It's not the only tractor around here.
إنها ليست الجرارة الوحيدة الموجودة هنا.
I'm the crazy fool for leaving my car here.
أنا المجنون الذي ترك سيارتي هنا.
I didn't even get to see the owner, and I only met a crazy jerk.
لم أتمكن حتى من رؤية المالك، ولم أقابل سوى شخص أحمق مجنون.
I'm a home shopping host from HIT Homeshopping.
أنا مقدمة برامج التسوق المنزلي من شركة HIT Homeshopping.
My name's Dam Ye-jin.
اسمي دام يي جين.
Mechoori?
ميتشوري؟
Hey, Mechoori.
مرحباً، ميتشوري.
What's he doing?
ماذا يفعل؟
Hey, Boss!
مرحباً يا رئيس!
What has you so deep in thought?
ما الذي يشغل بالك إلى هذا الحد؟
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
CHANGSIK HE DOESN'T BITE
تشانغسيك: إنه لا يعض
Changsik.
تشانغسيك.
Mechoori!
ميتشوري!
-Mechoori! -Hey, Sang-geum!
-ميتشوري! -مهلاً، سانغ-غوم!
Mechoori.
ميتشوري.
Som-yi.
سوم-يي.
What are you doing here? What about school?
ماذا تفعل هنا؟ وماذا عن المدرسة؟
Don't tell my sister.
لا تخبر أختي.
No.
لا.
You're in trouble now.
أنت في ورطة الآن.
You know what Mechoori's like.
أنت تعرف كيف هي ميتشوري.
Geez. Fine, I'll go.
يا إلهي. حسناً، سأذهب.
Gosh, you happened to come just in time for me to go to the market.
يا إلهي، لقد أتيت في الوقت المناسب تماماً لأذهب إلى السوق.
Geez, Mechoori came at this time on purpose.
يا إلهي، لقد جاء ميتشوري في هذا الوقت عن قصد.
I was just passing by.
كنتُ أمرّ من هنا فحسب.
You always give her a ride.
أنت دائماً توصلها بسيارتك.
-Som-yi. -Okay, I'm leaving.
-سوم-يي. -حسنًا، سأغادر.
-I'm only taking you up to the main road. -All right.
- سأوصلك فقط إلى الطريق الرئيسي. - حسناً.
Hello, I'm at the entrance of Deokpung Village.
مرحباً، أنا عند مدخل قرية دوكبونغ.
My rear wheel's stuck, and my side mirror's been smashed.
عجلتي الخلفية عالقة، ومرآة سيارتي الجانبية محطمة.
So I can't move.
لذا لا أستطيع التحرك.
What? It takes three hours?
ماذا؟ يستغرق الأمر ثلاث ساعات؟
I have a live show to do this evening.
لدي عرض مباشر سأقدمه هذا المساء.
I'm a host on TV.
أنا مقدم برامج تلفزيونية.
All right, then…
حسناً، إذاً...
Think, Ye-jin.
فكري يا يي جين.
You have to get back to Seoul in four hours.
عليك العودة إلى سيول في غضون أربع ساعات.
The bus! Right.
الحافلة! صحيح.
From Deokpung Village, Anyoung-gun…
من قرية دوكبونغ، ​​مقاطعة أنيونغ...
ANYOUNG-GUN, SEOUL
أنيونغ غان، سيول
The bus to Seoul…
الحافلة المتجهة إلى سيول...
STANDARD FARE 19,000 WON
الأجرة العادية 19,000 وون
I can take the 2:30 p.m. one.
يمكنني حضور الموعد الساعة 2:30 مساءً.
There's only 30 minutes left?
لم يتبق سوى 30 دقيقة؟
No way.
مستحيل.
Wait, stop!
انتظر، توقف!
Excuse me!
اعذرني!
Hey!
يا!
It's so breezy and nice.
الجو لطيف ومنعش للغاية.
-So nice. -Exactly.
- جميل جداً. - بالضبط.
Hey!
يا!
Wait!
انتظر!
Look at those clouds.
انظر إلى تلك الغيوم.
My goodness!
يا إلهي!
They're so beautiful!
إنها جميلة جداً!
Wait!
انتظر!
Hey!
يا!
Can you please give me a ride to the bus terminal?
هل يمكنك أن توصلني إلى محطة الحافلات؟
Hey…
يا…
Hey! Stop!
مهلاً! توقف!
-Mechoori! -Oh, my.
-ميتشوري! -يا إلهي.
Pull over, Mechoori!
توقف يا ميتشوري!
Hey, come on!
هيا بنا!
My goodness!
يا إلهي!
I said pull over!
قلتُ توقف!
-What do we do? -Oh, my.
- ماذا نفعل؟ - يا إلهي.
That hurts.
هذا مؤلم.
What do you want with that?
ماذا تريد من ذلك؟
What?
ماذا؟
It was just sticking out.
كان بارزاً فحسب.
Are you all right?
هل أنت بخير؟
Yes, I'm fine.
نعم، أنا بخير.
-Goodness. -You're not hurt anywhere?
يا إلهي! هل أنت بخير؟
You're so pretty.
أنتِ جميلة جداً.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Ma'am.
سيدتي.
The bus terminal…
محطة الحافلات...
Is it far from here?
هل هو بعيد من هنا؟
It'll take no time when you get on the bus.
لن يستغرق الأمر وقتاً طويلاً عندما تصعد إلى الحافلة.
That's a relief. Thank you.
هذا يُريحني. شكراً لك.
Gosh, I was almost too late.
يا إلهي، كدت أتأخر.
Ma'am, just a moment.
سيدتي، لحظة من فضلك.
Excuse me. Sorry.
معذرةً. آسف.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
You little…
يا لك من...
Gosh, you're a special guest from Seoul.
يا إلهي، أنت ضيف مميز من سيول.
You should sit in the best seat.
يجب أن تجلس في أفضل مقعد.
Right.
يمين.
Gosh, you're so pretty.
يا إلهي، أنتِ جميلة جداً.
Look how great her figure is.
انظروا كم هو رائع قوامها.
-And she's so slim. -She's just incredible!
- وهي نحيفة للغاية. - إنها رائعة حقاً!
It could rain tonight,
قد تمطر الليلة،
so close up and come early if business is slow.
لذا أغلقوا المكان واحضروا مبكراً إذا كان العمل بطيئاً.
Don't risk your lives for a few pennies.
لا تخاطروا بحياتكم من أجل بضعة بنسات.
-Goodness. Thanks. -Let's go.
- يا إلهي. شكراً. - هيا بنا.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Me. Help me.
أنا. ساعدني.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
There we go, Sang-geum.
ها نحن ذا، سانغ غوم.
Just you wait. I'll be back soon with a detailed repair estimate.
انتظر قليلاً. سأعود قريباً بتقدير مفصل لتكلفة الإصلاح.
-Come on, sweetie. -Yes, ma'am.
- هيا يا عزيزتي. - حاضر يا سيدتي.
Okay, get in.
حسناً، ادخل.
-Hurry up already. -All right.
- أسرعوا. - حسناً.
What's with all this stuff?
ما قصة كل هذه الأشياء؟
For goodness' sake.
يا إلهي!
TO MUPO
إلى موبو
Here we go.
ها نحن.
-Oh, my gosh! -My goodness!
يا إلهي! يا للعجب!
What's this?
ما هذا؟
What is he doing?
ماذا يفعل؟
-Are you all right? Oh, my gosh. -Yeah.
- هل أنت بخير؟ يا إلهي. - نعم.
My goodness.
يا إلهي.
Hey! What are you doing?
مرحباً! ماذا تفعل؟
What's your deal?
ما قصتك؟
That little… Is he crazy?
ذلك الصغير... هل هو مجنون؟
What?
ماذا؟
Are you trying to pick a fight?
هل تحاول افتعال شجار؟
Look at the clock, not me.
انظر إلى الساعة، لا إليّ.
It's 2:07 p.m.
الساعة الآن 2:07 مساءً
You're supposed to leave at 2:10 p.m.
من المفترض أن تغادر الساعة 2:10 مساءً
Is this your first time on a local bus?
هل هذه هي المرة الأولى التي تركب فيها حافلة محلية؟
Sometimes, we have to be flexible--
أحيانًا، علينا أن نكون مرنين.
This isn't the first time.
هذه ليست المرة الأولى.
And our village's meaning of "flexible"
ومعنى "المرونة" في قريتنا
is when the elders squeeze four cabbages of kimchi
يحدث ذلك عندما يقوم كبار السن بعصر أربع حبات من الكرنب لصنع الكيمتشي
into food containers for you instead of three.
في علب الطعام لك بدلاً من ثلاث.
For a bus that comes only twice a day with a five-hour gap,
بالنسبة لحافلة تأتي مرتين فقط في اليوم بفارق خمس ساعات،
it seems rules matter more than being flexible.
يبدو أن القواعد أهم من المرونة.
Hey, that's…
مهلاً، هذا...
Look…
ينظر…
Unbelievable!
لا يصدق!
Fine, then.
حسناً، إذاً.
We'll leave at 2:10 p.m.
سنغادر الساعة 2:10 مساءً
I'll do it.
سأفعل ذلك.
Are you all right?
هل أنت بخير؟
-You're not hurt, are you? -I'm fine.
- أنت لست مصاباً، أليس كذلك؟ - أنا بخير.
Are you all okay?
هل أنتم جميعاً بخير؟
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Do you have to sit here?
هل يجب عليك الجلوس هنا؟
What?
ماذا؟
PRIORITY SEAT
مقعد مميز
Oh, my gosh.
يا إلهي.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I keep losing face in front of him.
أشعر بالحرج الشديد أمامه.
Yes?
نعم؟
He'll be away from the farm for a while?
هل سيغيب عن المزرعة لفترة من الوقت؟
It seems he knew we'd come and avoided us on purpose.
يبدو أنه كان يعلم بقدومنا وتجنبنا عمداً.
Still, you did great.
مع ذلك، لقد أبليت بلاءً حسناً.
All right, bye.
حسنًا، مع السلامة.
PERFORMANCE REPORT FOR DAM YE-JIN
تقرير أداء دام يي جين
You did a background check?
هل أجريتَ فحصاً للخلفية؟
I told you.
أخبرتك.
I won't follow my sister's methods.
لن أتبع أساليب أختي.
There's something you must know.
هناك شيء يجب أن تعرفه.
While going over Ms. Dam's broadcast history,
أثناء استعراض تاريخ بث السيدة دام،
I noticed something strange.
لاحظت شيئاً غريباً.
Aside from her debut broadcast, she's never sold cosmetics.
باستثناء ظهورها الأول في البث، لم يسبق لها أن باعت مستحضرات تجميل.
So why would she personally send an offer to L'Étoile?
فلماذا ترسل هي شخصياً عرضاً إلى L'Étoile؟
I'm worried about her intentions.
أنا قلق بشأن نواياها.
To me, it just looks like she succeeded in launching new brands.
بالنسبة لي، يبدو الأمر وكأنها نجحت في إطلاق علامات تجارية جديدة.
Are we really looking at the same data?
هل نحن ننظر فعلاً إلى نفس البيانات؟
Please look at the last page, sir.
يرجى الاطلاع على الصفحة الأخيرة، سيدي.
2020 GOOD MORNING CREAM INCIDENT
حادثة كريم الصباح 2020
How does it feel to be at HIT?
ما هو شعورك بالتواجد في HIT؟
You mean, how does it feel to return to HIT?
هل تقصد، كيف تشعر بالعودة إلى HIT؟
We're allies now.
نحن حلفاء الآن.
Then, what will happen to Dam Ye-jin?
إذن، ماذا سيحدث لدام يي جين؟
We've crossed paths before, so it does bother me.
لقد تقاطعت طرقنا من قبل، لذا فإن الأمر يزعجني.
Right… You've met before.
صحيح... لقد التقيتما من قبل.
I'm thinking of letting her launch L'Étoile's essence.
أفكر في السماح لها بإطلاق جوهر عطر L'Étoile.
L'Étoile?
النجم؟
You're not putting her in charge of cosmetics again, are you?
لن تعينها على إدارة قسم مستحضرات التجميل مرة أخرى، أليس كذلك؟
It's been five years, and you've returned too.
لقد مرت خمس سنوات، وقد عدت أنت أيضاً.
The Dam Ye-jin of today can easily pull it off.
بإمكان دام يي جين الحالية أن تنجح في ذلك بسهولة.
Hyun-ki,
هيون كي،
are we really allies?
هل نحن حلفاء حقاً؟
Let's have our meal next time.
لنتناول وجبتنا في المرة القادمة.
I, Song Myeong-hwa, stake my name on this product
أنا، سونغ ميونغ هوا، أراهن باسمي على هذا المنتج
and confidently recommend it.
وأوصي به بثقة.
Our Good Morning Cream
كريم صباح الخير الخاص بنا
is safe for sensitive skin,
آمن للبشرة الحساسة،
and even infants and children can use it without worry.
وحتى الرضع والأطفال يمكنهم استخدامه دون قلق.
Good Morning Cream, the cream for your entire family.
كريم صباح الخير، الكريم المناسب لجميع أفراد عائلتك.
Try it out today.
جربها اليوم.
We just sold out!
لقد نفدت الكمية للتو!
A home shopping broadcast garnered buzz
أثار بثٌّ لبرامج التسوق المنزلي ضجةً كبيرة.
with the appearance of beloved actress Song Myeong-hwa.
بظهور الممثلة المحبوبة سونغ ميونغ هوا.
However, harmful substances were found in the cream they sold.
ومع ذلك، تم العثور على مواد ضارة في الكريم الذي كانوا يبيعونه.
Numerous users with inflammatory skin conditions
عدد كبير من المستخدمين يعانون من حالات جلدية التهابية
have suffered serious side effects.
لقد عانيت من آثار جانبية خطيرة.
As of today, I shall retire from my acting career.
اعتبارًا من اليوم، سأعتزل مهنة التمثيل.
Did you really use it yourself?
هل استخدمته بنفسك فعلاً؟
-Where's the apology to the victims? -Didn't you let people down?
أين الاعتذار للضحايا؟ ألم تخذل الناس؟
L'Étoile is a beauty brand that was launched seven years ago
L'Étoile هي علامة تجارية لمستحضرات التجميل تم إطلاقها قبل سبع سنوات
by the globally renowned French luxury group Desruets.
من قبل مجموعة ديسرويه الفرنسية الفاخرة ذات الشهرة العالمية .
It grew gradually at first with perfume and color cosmetics.
لقد نما هذا القطاع تدريجياً في البداية مع العطور ومستحضرات التجميل الملونة.
But three years ago,
لكن قبل ثلاث سنوات،
their product La Fin Essence went viral as soon as it was launched.
انتشر منتجهم "لا فين إيسنس" انتشاراً واسعاً بمجرد إطلاقه.
And now, L'Étoile is the signature brand of the group.
والآن، أصبحت L'Étoile العلامة التجارية المميزة للمجموعة.
And its Executive Director Eric Seo--
ومديرها التنفيذي إريك سيو--
-I have a question. -Yes?
لدي سؤال. - نعم؟
Why is his last name Seo?
لماذا يُطلق عليه اسم عائلة سيو؟
He's Korean, and his mother got remarried to Desruets' CEO.
هو كوري، وتزوجت والدته مرة أخرى من الرئيس التنفيذي لشركة ديسروتس.
By the way, Desruets' first wife was also Korean.
بالمناسبة، كانت زوجة ديسروتس الأولى كورية أيضاً.
And his eldest daughter is the Deputy CEO of L'Étoile.
وابنته الكبرى هي نائبة الرئيس التنفيذي لشركة L'Étoile.
This isn't the time for gossip.
ليس هذا وقت النميمة.
Right, I'll continue then.
حسناً، سأكمل إذن.
L'Étoile's signature item, La Fin Essence…
العنصر المميز لـ L'Étoile، La Fin Essence…
Dam Ye-jin, you're going to cross the line?
دام يي جين، هل ستتجاوزين الحدود؟
You think I didn't sell jewelry because I couldn't?
أتظن أنني لم أبع المجوهرات لأنني لم أستطع؟
Welcome. It's been such a long time.
أهلاً وسهلاً. لقد مر وقت طويل.
This way, please.
من هنا، من فضلك.
Can we secure enough stock of this
هل يمكننا تأمين مخزون كافٍ من هذا؟
so we can be on time for the holidays next month?
حتى نتمكن من الوصول في الوقت المناسب للعطلات الشهر المقبل؟
-Well, this is… -It's limited edition, right?
- حسنًا، هذا... - إنها طبعة محدودة، أليس كذلك؟
Well, for this one…
حسناً، بالنسبة لهذا الأمر...
Ms. Dam Ye-jin is already going to sell it, so…
السيدة دام يي جين ستبيعه بالفعل، لذا...
-Dam Ye-jin? -Yes.
-دام يي جين؟ - نعم.
It lacks a bit of detail.
ينقصها بعض التفاصيل.
-Yeah. The detail. -Right.
- أجل. التفاصيل. - صحيح.
Over here.
هنا.
What about this?
ماذا عن هذا؟
-Ms. Dam also picked this one… -My mistake.
- اختارت السيدة دام هذا أيضًا... - خطأي.
Instead…
بدلاً من…
This one!
هذا!
Ms. Dam picked that one as well.
السيدة دام اختارت ذلك أيضاً.
Are you kidding me? Everything's been taken by Dam Ye-jin.
هل تمزح معي؟ لقد استولت دام يي جين على كل شيء.
Are you telling me to sell the scraps?
هل تطلب مني بيع الخردة؟
No, of course not!
لا، بالطبع لا!
What about that one?
ماذا عن هذا؟
This is so adorable!
هذا رائع للغاية!
Isn't it cute?
أليس هذا لطيفاً؟
This feature is cute.
هذه الميزة لطيفة.
Can we get enough stock?
هل يمكننا الحصول على كمية كافية من المخزون؟
Yes, Ms. Dam said the keychain was too flashy, so she didn't pick--
نعم، قالت السيدة دام إن سلسلة المفاتيح كانت لافتة للنظر للغاية، لذلك لم تخترها.
I won't sell it either then! I won't!
لن أبيعها أنا أيضاً! لن أفعل!
It seems Ms. Dong has struck first.
يبدو أن السيدة دونغ قد بدأت بالهجوم أولاً.
AUGUST 16, FIRST LAUNCH IN KOREA ONLY AT HIT
١٦ أغسطس، الإطلاق الأول في كوريا حصرياً لدى HIT
Hey.
يا.
You said you didn't do cosmetics. Is this about losing your slot?
قلتِ إنكِ لا تعملين في مجال مستحضرات التجميل. هل يتعلق الأمر بفقدان مكانكِ؟
Yun-ji.
يون جي.
I didn't agree to this, so don't get so worked up.
لم أوافق على هذا، لذا لا تنزعج كثيراً.
The date's right there. You think I'm stupid?
التاريخ واضح. أتظنني غبياً؟
Hey.
يا.
Is this your revenge?
هل هذا انتقامك؟
-Are you scared? -Hey!
- هل أنت خائف؟ - مهلاً!
What do you think you're doing?
ما الذي تظن نفسك فاعلاً؟
Ms. Dong.
السيدة دونغ.
What's that ad?
ما هذا الإعلان؟
It's exactly what you see.
الأمر كما تراه تماماً.
But unfortunately,
لكن لسوء الحظ،
Ye-jin says she didn't agree to it.
تقول يي جين إنها لم توافق على ذلك.
You can't do it?
ألا تستطيع فعل ذلك؟
Are you going to stab your colleagues in the back?
هل ستطعن ​​زملاءك في الظهر؟
They're still relying on you though.
لكنهم ما زالوا يعتمدون عليك.
Ms. Dong.
السيدة دونغ.
DAM YE-JIN
دام يي جين
Ms. Michelle sent these. She said you'd love them.
أرسلت السيدة ميشيل هذه. وقالت إنها ستعجبك.
This is what my sister's like.
هذا ما يشبه أختي.
Mr. Cha, pick one for me.
سيد تشا، اختر لي واحداً.
Me?
أنا؟
Pick anything. They're all great albums.
اختر أي شيء. جميعها ألبومات رائعة.
What will be the first record I listen to in Korea?
ما هو أول ألبوم سأستمع إليه في كوريا؟
I'm excited.
أنا متحمس.
Pardon?
عفو؟
This umbrella.
هذه المظلة.
Where did you buy it?
من أين اشتريته؟
-It stopped. -You're right.
- لقد توقف. - أنت محق.
This place…
هذا المكان...
-Do you know this place? -Yes.
- هل تعرف هذا المكان؟ - نعم.
I came here once but I forgot the name, so I'd been searching for it.
لقد أتيت إلى هنا مرة واحدة لكنني نسيت الاسم، لذلك كنت أبحث عنه.
I can't believe I found it.
لا أصدق أنني وجدته.
You have to try their croissants. They're the best I've ever had.
يجب أن تجرب الكرواسون لديهم. إنه الأفضل الذي تناولته على الإطلاق.
I totally recommend them.
أوصي بهم بشدة.
Would you like to have lunch here tomorrow?
هل ترغب بتناول الغداء هنا غداً؟
Sounds good.
ًيبدو جيدا.
Good.
جيد.
Well…
حسنًا…
I know this might sound strange,
أعلم أن هذا قد يبدو غريباً،
but do you believe in fate?
لكن هل تؤمن بالقدر؟
What?
ماذا؟
If you believe in fate,
إذا كنت تؤمن بالقدر،
why don't we just meet here tomorrow?
لماذا لا نلتقي هنا غداً؟
I guess you two weren't destined to be together.
أظن أنكما لم تكونا مقدرين لبعضكما.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I thought that too, but maybe I was wrong.
كنت أعتقد ذلك أيضاً، لكن ربما كنت مخطئاً.
Pardon?
عفو؟
I'm going to make it happen this time.
سأنجح في ذلك هذه المرة.
Mechoori.
ميتشوري.
There's a leak in the house.
يوجد تسريب في المنزل.
You said there was a leak.
قلتَ إن هناك تسريباً.
I wanted you to have some potatoes.
أردتُ أن تُعطيك بعض البطاطا.
I can't eat all this.
لا أستطيع أن آكل كل هذا.
Don't be so cold.
لا تكن بارداً جداً.
Then, I'll just throw them away.
ثم سأرميها ببساطة.
Three…
ثلاثة…
I'll just have three. I usually skip breakfast.
سأكتفي بثلاثة فقط. عادةً ما أتجاوز وجبة الإفطار.
Five. I'm going to count them.
خمسة. سأقوم بعدّهم.
Thank you for the food.
شكراً على الطعام.
Everyone, it feels like I'm walking through a cypress forest right now.
يا جماعة، أشعر وكأنني أسير الآن في غابة من أشجار السرو.
How should I explain this?
كيف أشرح هذا؟
Hey, isn't she that girl?
أليست هي تلك الفتاة؟
I feel refreshed as soon as I take a breath.
I feel refreshed as soon as I take a breath.
For all of you who are busy with work…
For all of you who are busy with work…
Is that a zero or an eight?
Is that a zero or an eight?
…this is the perfect product.
…this is the perfect product.
Look at this.
Look at this.
Hey, Mechoori.
Hey, Mechoori.
Press the numbers for me.
Press the numbers for me.
I need to buy one of those.
I need to buy one of those.
The warmth spreads through your whole body.
The warmth spreads through your whole body.
Do you see all this sweat?
Do you see all this sweat?
What are you doing? I have to buy it before they sell out.
What are you doing? I have to buy it before they sell out.
Just go to a sauna. I'll take you.
Just go to a sauna. I'll take you.
There's no need to go to a sauna in this hot weather.
There's no need to go to a sauna in this hot weather.
-Just do it comfortably at home. -That's all exaggerated advertising.
-Just do it comfortably at home. -That's all exaggerated advertising.
The 5,000 reviews on their official site prove how effective this is.
The 5,000 reviews on their official site prove how effective this is.
So I can recommend it with confidence.
So I can recommend it with confidence.
Ma'am, don't fall for such tactics and waste your money.
Ma'am, don't fall for such tactics and waste your money.
-Give it some thought. -There's no time to think.
-Give it some thought. -There's no time to think.
Today's the last time you'll be able to buy these at this price.
Today's the last time you'll be able to buy these at this price.
Hurry up and order it!
Hurry up and order it!
And Package 3 has just sold out.
And Package 3 has just sold out.
Your name is Yang Sang-geum, right?
Your name is Yang Sang-geum, right?
Yeah.
Yeah.
-And your resident registration number? -My ID number?
-And your resident registration number? -My ID number?
What was it again?
What was it again?
It's 470528.
It's 470528.
ENTER YOUR RESIDENT REGISTRATION NUMBER
ENTER YOUR RESIDENT REGISTRATION NUMBER
That's not it.
That's not it.
Then, it must be 460528.
Then, it must be 460528.
That's not it either.
That's not it either.
Maybe 460628?
Maybe 460628?
No. Where's your ID card?
No. Where's your ID card?
I never use it, so I don't know where it is.
I never use it, so I don't know where it is.
I'll just use my info then.
I'll just use my info then.
How much should I give you?
How much should I give you?
It's fine. This is for the potatoes.
It's fine. This is for the potatoes.
We'll begin the prize drawing.
We'll begin the prize drawing.
For our customers who ordered through our mobile app,
For our customers who ordered through our mobile app,
we'll begin a prize draw
we'll begin a prize draw
to win an additional bathtub.
to win an additional bathtub.
CONGRATULATIONS DEOKPUNG VILLAGE, LEE * SEOK
CONGRATULATIONS DEOKPUNG VILLAGE, LEE * SEOK
Mr. Lee from Deokpung Village, Anyoung-gun.
Mr. Lee from Deokpung Village, Anyoung-gun.
Congratulations.
Congratulations.
Deokpung Village!
Deokpung Village!
CONGRATULATIONS, LEE HAE-SEOK!
CONGRATULATIONS, LEE HAE-SEOK!
YOU WON OUR BUY ONE, GET ONE FREE EVENT
YOU WON OUR BUY ONE, GET ONE FREE EVENT
HIT HOMESHOPPING DELIVERED TO YOUR DOOR WITH CARE
HIT HOMESHOPPING DELIVERED TO YOUR DOOR WITH CARE
Changsik.
Changsik.
Changsik, why are you barking so loudly?
Changsik, why are you barking so loudly?
Hello.
Hello.
Oh, my. Look who it is!
Oh, my. Look who it is!
Darling, I knew I'd seen you somewhere before.
Darling, I knew I'd seen you somewhere before.
You looked so familiar.
You looked so familiar.
I saw you were on TV.
I saw you were on TV.
Wait. Let me boil you some chicken.
Wait. Let me boil you some chicken.
No, it's fine.
No, it's fine.
Potatoes like these grown in rich soil with clean air
Potatoes like these grown in rich soil with clean air
are difficult to find in Seoul.
are difficult to find in Seoul.
By the way, what are you doing here?
By the way, what are you doing here?
You ordered a bathtub from our home shopping channel.
You ordered a bathtub from our home shopping channel.
Of course. I bought what you were selling.
Of course. I bought what you were selling.
Congratulations on winning your prize!
تهانينا على فوزك بالجائزة!
I won a prize?
هل فزت بجائزة؟
Yes. Your husband is Mr. Lee, right?
نعم. زوجك هو السيد لي، أليس كذلك؟
Who's that? My husband's name is Moon Gwon-pyeong.
من هذا؟ اسم زوجي مون غوون بيونغ.
This was the address though.
لكن هذا هو العنوان.
Then, do you know a Mr. "Lee something Seok"?
إذن، هل تعرف السيد "لي شيء ما سيوك"؟
"Lee something Seok"? Who could that be?
"لي شيء ما سيوك"؟ من عساه يكون؟
He lives way over there.
إنه يعيش هناك في مكان بعيد.
Let's see. Go around this way and here.
لنرى. اسلك هذا الطريق وهذا الطريق.
Okay, this must be it.
حسناً، لا بد أن هذا هو الأمر.
Anyone home? You have a package.
هل يوجد أحد في المنزل؟ لديك طرد.
Mr. "Lee something Seok"?
السيد "لي شيء سيوك"؟
Are you home, sir?
هل أنت في المنزل يا سيدي؟
Mr. Lee!
السيد لي!
I'm not expecting any packages…
لا أتوقع وصول أي طرود...
Are you Mr. "Lee something Seok"?
هل أنت السيد "لي شيء سيوك"؟
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
How did you know my address?
كيف عرفت عنواني؟
I'm here to deliver Mr. "Lee something Seok" his prize.
أنا هنا لأسلم السيد "لي شيء سيوك" جائزته.
For privacy reasons, the middle character of your name is hidden.
لأسباب تتعلق بالخصوصية، تم إخفاء الحرف الأوسط من اسمك.
What's your full name?
ما اسمك الكامل؟
It's Matthew. Leave it here. I'll give it to him later.
إنه ماثيو. اتركه هنا. سأعطيه إياه لاحقاً.
So your father must be Mr. "Lee something Seok."
إذن، لا بد أن والدك هو السيد "لي شيء ما سيوك".
Then, I guess "Mechoori" means Matthew Lee,
إذن، أعتقد أن "ميتشوري" تعني ماثيو لي،
not "mechoori" as in quail.
ليس "mechoori" كما في السمان.
That's so funny. She calls you "quail"…
هذا مضحك جداً. إنها تناديك "السمان"...
MATTHEW LEE
ماثيو لي
MECHOORI
ميشور
It's funny.
إنه أمر مضحك.
I guess you watch my show. You should've told me.
أظن أنك تشاهد برنامجي. كان عليك أن تخبرني.
If that's all, you should leave.
إذا كان هذا كل شيء، فعليك المغادرة.
I came all the way here. I can't just go. Is your father inside?
لقد قطعت كل هذه المسافة. لا يمكنني الرحيل هكذا. هل والدك بالداخل؟
No, he's not.
لا، ليس كذلك.
How come everyone in this village is absent?
لماذا يغيب جميع سكان هذه القرية؟
Is everybody away on vacation or what?
هل الجميع في إجازة أم ماذا؟
When will he come back?
متى سيعود؟
-He won't be here-- -"He won't be here for a while."
-لن يكون هنا-- -"لن يكون هنا لفترة من الوقت."
I knew it. That's your go-to move, isn't it?
كنت أعرف ذلك. هذه هي خطوتك المعتادة، أليس كذلك؟
You said the farm owner wouldn't be here for a while too…
قلتَ أيضاً إن صاحب المزرعة لن يكون هنا لفترة من الوقت...
Oh, my gosh! Is your father the owner?
يا إلهي! هل والدك هو المالك؟
No. Please, just leave now.
لا. من فضلك، ارحل الآن.
Could you at least give me his number?
هل يمكنك على الأقل أن تعطيني رقمه؟
Why did you come here?
لماذا أتيت إلى هنا؟
I'm here for one thing. To meet the farm owner.
أنا هنا لسبب واحد. لمقابلة صاحب المزرعة.
If you're that desperate, make an official appointment.
إذا كنت يائساً إلى هذه الدرجة، فحدد موعداً رسمياً.
Don't barge in here like this.
لا تقتحموا المكان هكذا.
Thanks for the advice,
شكراً على النصيحة.
but instead of that…
لكن بدلاً من ذلك...
I'll do it my way.
سأفعل ذلك على طريقتي.
Geez, he's so cold.
يا إلهي، إنه بارد جداً.
He wouldn't help me until the very end.
لم يساعدني إلا في النهاية.
But I'm never going to give up.
لكنني لن أستسلم أبداً.
I'm back.
لقد عدت.
It's late. Have dinner before you go. I'll boil some chicken for you.
لقد تأخر الوقت. تناول العشاء قبل أن تذهب. سأقوم بسلق بعض الدجاج لك.
It's fine. If I take a taxi, it'll be quick.
لا بأس. إذا استقللت سيارة أجرة، فسيكون الأمر سريعاً.
You're taking a taxi all the way to Seoul?
هل ستستقل سيارة أجرة طوال الطريق إلى سيول؟
Goodness, that's a huge waste of money.
يا إلهي، هذا تبذير كبير للمال.
It's really okay…
لا بأس حقاً...
Ma'am, do you know the mushroom farm over there?
سيدتي، هل تعرفين مزرعة الفطر هناك؟
Of course. I work there and receive pay too.
بالتأكيد. أنا أعمل هناك وأتقاضى راتباً أيضاً.
Actually, you're right. It's kind of late to head back to Seoul.
في الحقيقة، أنت محق. لقد فات الأوان نوعاً ما للعودة إلى سيول.
Is it okay if I sleep over just for tonight?
هل من المقبول أن أبيت عندكم هذه الليلة فقط؟
Goodness, what on earth?
يا إلهي، ما هذا بحق السماء؟
These little… Come out here for a second, darling!
هؤلاء الصغار... تعالوا إلى هنا للحظة يا عزيزتي!
Okay. Is there something wrong…
حسناً. هل هناك خطب ما؟
What are you doing? Hurry and grab the chickens!
ماذا تفعل؟ أسرع واقبض على الدجاج!
Yes, ma'am.
نعم يا سيدتي.
Ma'am, I'll catch them!
سيدتي، سأقبض عليهم!
Damn it. Hey!
اللعنة! مهلاً!
Oh, my gosh. They're going nuts.
يا إلهي. إنهم يجنون.
It's trying to stop me!
إنها تحاول إيقافي!
They're running.
إنهم يركضون.
I'll catch them, ma'am. Damn it.
سأقبض عليهم يا سيدتي. اللعنة.
Why are they so fast?
لماذا هم بهذه السرعة؟
Damn it.
عليك اللعنة.
What?
ماذا؟
Hey!
يا!
Hey! Hey, Changsik!
يا! يا تشانغسيك!
SANG-GEUM'S CHICKEN, YE-JIN
دجاج سانج جيوم، يي جين
You're dead meat.
أنت في ورطة كبيرة.
Hey!
يا!
Stop right there!
توقف هنا!
Hey! Stop right there!
مهلاً! توقف هنا!
I got you!
حصلت عليك!
You little…
يا لك من...
Hey!
يا!
What do I do?
ماذا أفعل؟
Geez.
يا إلهي.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Well, the thing is…
حسناً، الأمر هو...
Is this the way you were talking about?
هل هذه هي الطريقة التي كنت تتحدث عنها؟
No, I…
لا، أنا...
This is a misunderstanding.
هذا سوء فهم.
So…
لذا…
Ms. Yang's chicken flew over your fence
دجاجة السيدة يانغ طارت فوق سياجك
and went into your house.
ودخل منزلك.
-A chicken? -Yes, a chicken.
- دجاجة؟ - نعم، دجاجة.
I'd like to make a report.
أود تقديم تقرير.
Well, I looked everywhere, but there was no trace of a chicken.
حسناً، لقد بحثت في كل مكان، لكن لم يكن هناك أي أثر للدجاجة.
What? That's impossible…
ماذا؟ هذا مستحيل…
I swear, the chicken flew over the fence like this.
أقسم بالله، لقد طارت الدجاجة فوق السياج هكذا.
Could we have a talk?
هل يمكننا التحدث؟
No, thank you.
لا، شكراً.
Come on.
تعال.
Just for a second.
للحظة واحدة فقط.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Look.
ينظر.
Do you really have to go this far?
هل يجب عليك حقاً أن تذهب إلى هذا الحد؟
I'm pretty well-known.
أنا معروف إلى حد ما.
What if they write articles about me?
ماذا لو كتبوا مقالات عني؟
That sounds like a meaningless concern.
يبدو هذا وكأنه قلق لا معنى له.
It flew over the fence?
طار فوق السياج؟
Maybe it dug underground.
ربما حفرت تحت الأرض.
For now, let's go and talk at the station.
الآن، دعنا نذهب ونتحدث في المحطة.
What?
ماذا؟
Wait. Just a moment.
انتظر. لحظة من فضلك.
I'm going to argue that we're both at fault.
سأجادل بأننا كلانا مخطئ.
Isn't a hit-and-run a more serious offense than trespassing?
أليس حادث الدهس والفرار جريمة أكثر خطورة من التعدي على الممتلكات؟
Oh, right.
أوه، صحيح.
We have experts in this field right here.
لدينا خبراء في هذا المجال هنا.
Officers.
الضباط.
Ms. Dam.
السيدة دام.
Let's talk this over.
دعنا نتحدث في هذا الأمر.
You should've trusted what I said.
كان عليك أن تثق بما قلته.
How much is the repair cost?
كم تبلغ تكلفة الإصلاح؟
It's going to be at least 10 million won.
سيكون سعره 10 ملايين وون على الأقل.
It's limited edition.
إنها نسخة محدودة.
But I'm not that cruel.
لكنني لستُ بتلك القسوة.
There's a simple and easy way to resolve this matter.
هناك طريقة بسيطة وسهلة لحل هذه المسألة.
If you give me the farm owner's number, I'll pretend it didn't happen.
إذا أعطيتني رقم صاحب المزرعة، فسأتظاهر بأن الأمر لم يحدث.
All right.
حسنًا.
What's his number?
ما هو رقمه؟
I'll give you the 10 million won.
سأعطيك العشرة ملايين وون.
What?
ماذا؟
I mean, I didn't even get a proper estimate yet.
أعني، لم أحصل حتى على تقدير مناسب بعد.
I don't want to be involved in this matter anymore.
لا أريد أن أكون متورطاً في هذا الأمر بعد الآن.
So let's resolve it now.
فلنحل الأمر الآن.
Fine. I'd be so grateful for that.
حسناً. سأكون ممتناً جداً لذلك.
Wait.
انتظر.
Are you free for a moment?
هل أنت متفرغ للحظة؟
AGREEMENT
اتفاق
Do we really have to go this far?
هل يجب علينا حقاً أن نذهب إلى هذا الحد؟
Then, I'll make an official complaint to HIT
ثم سأقدم شكوى رسمية إلى شركة HIT
that their host used an event to gain private information--
أن مضيفهم استغل الحدث للحصول على معلومات خاصة.
I didn't say I wouldn't do it.
لم أقل إنني لن أفعل ذلك.
I'm writing this clearly in big letters.
أكتب هذا بوضوح وبأحرف كبيرة.
"I, Dam Ye-jin…"
"أنا، دام يي جين..."
"…promise to never…"
"...أعدك ألا..."
-"…promise to never visit Mechoori's…" -Matthew.
-"...أعدك ألا تزور ميتشوري أبدًا..." -ماثيو.
"…promise to never visit Matthew Lee's house again."
"...أعدك ألا أزور منزل ماثيو لي مرة أخرى."
-Happy? -No. Write the address too.
-هل أنت سعيد؟ -لا. اكتب العنوان أيضاً.
Ridiculous…
سخيف…
L'Étoile keeps requesting another meeting.
تستمر صحيفة "ليتوال" في طلب عقد اجتماع آخر.
It's so annoying.
إنه أمر مزعج للغاية.
Don't worry. I told them clearly that we're not renewing the contract.
لا تقلق. لقد أخبرتهم بوضوح أننا لن نجدد العقد.
Isn't it time to go home?
أليس الوقت قد حان للعودة إلى المنزل؟
Your routine's more precise than my limited edition watch.
روتينك أكثر دقة من ساعتي ذات الإصدار المحدود.
Something came up, so I'm behind on work.
طرأ أمرٌ ما، لذا أنا متأخر في العمل.
Gosh, I see.
يا إلهي، فهمت.
-Let's try again. -If you're here to say that, just go.
- لنحاول مرة أخرى. - إذا كنت هنا لتقول ذلك، فاذهب فحسب.
See? After what the renowned L'Étoile did, we can't trust anyone.
أرأيتم؟ بعد ما فعلته صحيفة "ليتوال" الشهيرة، لا يمكننا الوثوق بأحد.
Let's use these mushrooms ourselves instead of giving them away.
دعونا نستخدم هذه الفطريات بأنفسنا بدلاً من توزيعها على الآخرين.
You can manage everything from beginning to end.
يمكنك إدارة كل شيء من البداية إلى النهاية.
-Mu-won… -You did what you could.
-مو-وون… -لقد فعلت ما بوسعك.
Can't you focus on what you've done until now
ألا يمكنك التركيز على ما أنجزته حتى الآن؟
instead of that day?
بدلاً من ذلك اليوم؟
I'm Kang Mu-won, the guy who never gives up!
أنا كانغ مو وون، الرجل الذي لا يستسلم أبداً!
So can't you give up instead?
ألا يمكنك الاستسلام بدلاً من ذلك؟
Get inside.
ادخل إلى الداخل.
These little brats.
هؤلاء الأطفال المزعجون.
What a chaotic day.
يا له من يوم فوضوي!
But who on earth is he though?
لكن من يكون هذا الشخص يا ترى؟
A former celebrity?
شخصية مشهورة سابقة؟
A conglomerate heir?
وريث مجموعة شركات؟
No way. Is he hiding here after committing fraud?
مستحيل. هل يختبئ هنا بعد ارتكابه عملية احتيال؟
No, that's not it.
لا، ليس هذا هو الأمر.
He doesn't look like a criminal.
لا يبدو عليه أنه مجرم.
But otherwise, I don't see a reason to act like that.
لكن بخلاف ذلك، لا أرى سبباً للتصرف على هذا النحو.
What could it be?
ما الذي يمكن أن يكون؟
Hang on.
انتظر لحظة.
I didn't come here to catch chickens.
لم آتِ إلى هنا لأصطاد الدجاج.
I'm not going home empty-handed this time.
لن أعود إلى المنزل خالي الوفاض هذه المرة.
So these must be the white flower noori mushrooms.
إذن لا بد أن هذه هي فطر النوري ذو الزهرة البيضاء.
They look much better in person.
تبدو أفضل بكثير على الطبيعة.
Wait!
انتظر!
Come on.
تعال.
This isn't your farm.
هذه ليست مزرعتك.
Earlier, we were at your house,
كنا في منزلك في وقت سابق،
but this place isn't yours, so you can't claim any rights here.
لكن هذا المكان ليس ملكك، لذا لا يمكنك المطالبة بأي حقوق هنا.
Even if I do get reported, the farm owner should be doing it.
حتى لو تم الإبلاغ عني، يجب على صاحب المزرعة أن يفعل ذلك.
I'm the farm supervisor.
أنا مشرف المزرعة.
Come on. I already saw the farm supervisor last time.
هيا. لقد رأيت مشرف المزرعة في المرة الماضية.
If you want to chase me out, then call the farm owner
إذا كنت تريد طردي، فاتصل بصاحب المزرعة.
and tell him to come here right now.
وأخبره أن يأتي إلى هنا الآن.
What do you think you're doing?
ما الذي تظن نفسك فاعلاً؟
A farm tour.
جولة في مزرعة.
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
Do you know how much I studied about these mushrooms?
هل تعلم كم درست عن هذه الفطريات؟
Hey!
يا!
They boost skin elasticity, reduce pore size, and have antioxidant benefits.
فهي تعزز مرونة الجلد، وتقلل من حجم المسام، ولها فوائد مضادة للأكسدة.
I knew they were amazing, but I had to see for myself.
كنت أعرف أنهم رائعون، لكن كان عليّ أن أرى ذلك بنفسي.
Wait!
انتظر!
You can't enter…
لا يمكنك الدخول…
I take back my word. Let me apologize.
أتراجع عن كلامي. اسمحوا لي بالاعتذار.
This farm isn't just amazing.
هذه المزرعة ليست مذهلة فحسب.
Hang on.
انتظر لحظة.
Yes?
نعم؟
What?
ماذا؟
What is it?
ما هذا؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Did you just enter this farm
هل دخلت للتو هذه المزرعة؟
carrying stuff like this?
هل تحمل أشياء كهذه؟
CHICKEN FEATHER
ريشة دجاج
Gosh, what is this doing here?
يا إلهي، ما الذي يفعله هذا هنا؟
Get out.
اخرج.
But…
لكن…
There's a bug!
هناك خلل!
Right here. And here too.
هنا بالضبط. وهنا أيضاً.
Is this really okay?
هل هذا مقبول حقاً؟
You shouldn't be nagging me about hygiene right now.
لا ينبغي أن تزعجني بشأن النظافة الآن.
It's proof that they're organic.
هذا دليل على أنها عضوية.
How can I believe that?
كيف لي أن أصدق ذلك؟
You're interrupting my work, so please leave.
أنت تقاطع عملي، لذا أرجو منك المغادرة.
But why are you working late all alone?
لكن لماذا تعملين لوقت متأخر بمفردك؟
Do the elders make you do everything since you're the youngest?
هل يُجبرك الكبار على فعل كل شيء لأنك الأصغر؟
Oh, dear.
يا عزيزي.
That jerk.
ذلك الأحمق.
Gosh, those branches…
يا إلهي، تلك الأغصان...
Don't touch the mushrooms.
لا تلمس الفطر.
You'll lower their value.
ستؤدي إلى انخفاض قيمتها.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
What?
ماذا؟
When do you get off work?
متى تنتهي من العمل؟
When I think I've done enough.
عندما أعتقد أنني قد أنجزت ما يكفي.
I think I've done enough here too.
أعتقد أنني قد فعلت ما يكفي هنا أيضاً.
Ms. Dong.
السيدة دونغ.
I'll do the launch
سأقوم بالإطلاق
for L'Étoile.
لـ L'Étoile.
-Hello? -Hey.
-مرحباً؟ -أهلاً.
Have you put some thought
هل فكرت في الأمر قليلاً؟
into our dreams and future--
في أحلامنا ومستقبلنا-
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Hello…
مرحبًا…
That's enough, all right?
هذا يكفي، حسناً؟
Hello?
مرحباً؟
Who is this?
من هذا؟
Have you thought about it?
هل فكرت في الأمر؟
What?
ماذا؟
I'm Kang Dong-koo from Gangdong-gu.
أنا كانغ دونغ كو من غانغدونغ غو.
Hey, Dong-koo.
مرحباً، دونغ كو.
Tell your uncle that if he keeps this up,
أخبر عمك أنه إذا استمر على هذا المنوال،
I'm changing my number.
سأغير رقمي.
Hey, why would you do that? Wait!
مهلاً، لماذا تفعل ذلك؟ انتظر!
AGREEMENT
اتفاق
I, DAM YE-JIN, PROMISE TO NEVER VISIT MATTHEW LEE'S HOUSE AGAIN
أنا، دام يي جين، أعدك ألا أزور منزل ماثيو لي مرة أخرى.
Moon Gwon-pyeong.
مون غوون بيونغ.
Let's meet in my dreams.
لنلتقي في أحلامي.
Are you comfortable?
هل أنت مرتاح؟
It's nice and cool, right?
الجو لطيف وبارد، أليس كذلك؟
Yes, very cool.
نعم، رائع جداً.
Goodness.
يا إلهي.
By the way, ma'am.
بالمناسبة يا سيدتي.
You said you work at the mushroom farm.
قلت إنك تعمل في مزرعة الفطر.
Do you know the owner's number?
هل تعرف رقم المالك؟
His number?
رقمه؟
We see each other every day. Why would I call him?
نلتقي كل يوم. لماذا أتصل به؟
Get some sleep.
احصل على قسط من النوم.
-Okay, good night. -Good night.
- حسنًا، تصبح على خير. - تصبح على خير.
-Sleep tight. -Okay.
- حسناً.
It's only 10:00 p.m.
الساعة العاشرة مساءً فقط
No way I'd be sleepy right now.
مستحيل أن أشعر بالنعاس الآن.
This won't do.
هذا لن ينفع.
OWL, GRASSHOPPER, CICADA, CRICKET, CLICK BEETLE
بومة، جرادة، زيز، صرصور الليل، خنفساء النقر
FRIDAY, AUGUST 1
الجمعة، 1 أغسطس
It's only midnight?
هل الساعة منتصف الليل فقط؟
Is this for real?
هل هذا حقيقي؟
Hey, Hae-seok.
مرحباً، هايسوك.
Let's give it another try.
لنحاول مرة أخرى.
Here's an acrostic. Give me the syllables.
إليكِ قصيدة رأسية. أعطني المقاطع الصوتية.
No, I'll do it myself.
لا، سأفعل ذلك بنفسي.
Lee, please, Hae-seok
لي، من فضلك، هاي سوك
Hae, I'm begging you, Hae-seok
هاي، أتوسل إليك يا هاي سوك
Seok, you're making me upset too
سيوك، أنت تزعجني أيضاً.
What do you think?
ما رأيك؟
CHANGE PHONE NUMBER
تغيير رقم الهاتف
YOUR NUMBER HAS BEEN CHANGED
تم تغيير رقمك
-Who is this-- -Mom.
- من هذه؟ - أمي.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Mom, why weren't you picking up?
أمي، لماذا لم تجيبي على الهاتف؟
SOLD OUT ON YOU
نفدت الكمية لديك
THANKS TO SPECIAL GUEST AHN SANG-WOO
شكرًا للضيف المميز آن سانغ وو
You look so good together.
تبدوان رائعين معاً.
I'm sorry about yesterday's misunderstanding.
أعتذر عن سوء الفهم الذي حدث بالأمس.
I totally get it. Let's call it even.
أفهم ذلك تماماً. فلنعتبر الأمر منتهياً.
Dam Ye-jin?
سد يي جين؟
Hello, this is Dam Ye-jin, your agent for today.
مرحباً، هذه دام يي جين، وكيلتكم لهذا اليوم.
Is this HIT? This is how you handle things?
هل هذا نجاح؟ هل هذه هي طريقتك في التعامل مع الأمور؟
I'm here today because you called me.
أنا هنا اليوم لأنك اتصلت بي.
Will you please leave?
هل يمكنك المغادرة من فضلك؟
Mr. Lee!
السيد لي!
What was she doing here?
ماذا كانت تفعل هنا؟
You really don't recognize me?
ألا تعرفني حقاً؟
Let's end things with L'Étoile for good.
لننهي الأمور مع L'Étoile إلى الأبد.
You sure you won't regret it? This is L'Étoile.
هل أنت متأكد أنك لن تندم؟ هذا هو L'Étoile.
You don't have anything to say to me?
أليس لديك ما تقوله لي؟
I hope we don't cross paths again.
أتمنى ألا نلتقي مجدداً.
Subtitle translation by: Juyoung Park
ترجمة الترجمة الفرعية: جويونغ بارك